HIROSHI KOMIYAMA

SKILLS

Language

Javascript · Typescript · C++ · C# · PHP · Python · Java · HTML · CSS

Frameworks

 $React \cdot Vue \cdot Angular JS \cdot Angular \ 2+ \cdot$

React Native · Laravel · Flutter ·

Django · Next.js · Express.js · Nuxt.js

Libraries/APIs

 $\mathsf{D3.js} \cdot \mathsf{jQuery} \cdot \mathsf{WebRTC} \cdot \mathsf{Socket.IO}$

Tools

AWS · Git · Github · Jira · Trello ·

Mocha · Webpack · Babel

Platforms

MacOS · Docker · AWS Lambda ·

Windows

Storage

MySQL · MongoDB · AWS S3 ·

Amazon DynamoDB

LANGUAGES

English

Proficient



Chinese Intermediate



PASSIONS

Problem solving and collaboration

Web and Mobile Developer

\$\ +19569045018 @ champion5star247963@gmail.com

RESUME PROFILE

I'm a passionate, enthusiastic, and professional Full-Stack Developer who loves nothing more than creating and developing many kinds of web and mobile apps using all the skills I've acquired over 6 years of dedication to studying and developing. My goal with all my clients is to listen, learn, understand, and execute to the highest level. I always aim to deliver what the client requires, but if I feel there's a better solution, I'm always willing to give them some input and direction if wanted. A happy client is a successful project to me

EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer

06/2016 - 11/2017

ITM HOUSE

Toronto, Canada

ITM House is an agile software development company.

They were founded in 2011 and have a team of 11 employees who specialize in custom software development, Al, and blockchain development.

- Created reusable D3.js charts using Raphael.js to draw SVG on browsers.
- · Handled responsive design layouts for views.
- Implemented reusable components for UX using jQuery.
- Created an xQuery Selector generator from an HTML Element DOMNode.
- · Created a Pop CSS editor for elements.

Web Developer

11/2017 - 07/2019

NOVISMART TECH.

Wien, Austria

NOVISMART TECH. Is a business consulting company. Founded in 2013, the small team offers business consulting, custom software development, IoT development, wearable app development, and more.

- · Created a new front-end app based on React and Redux.
- Added a Hot module replacement plugin to Webpack.
- Worked with legacy code on the server side, able to understand the principles behind it and make it work again.

Senior Full Stack Developer

01/2020 - 03/2022

CodeEpsilon

Lewes, US

CodeEpsilon is a leading Custom Software Development Company in India & US providing a spectrum of IT services, including IT Consulting, Mobile App Development, Web Development, Creative Design (UI/UX), DevOps, Support, and Maintenance, Migration Service, and Quality Assurance.

- · Worked on providing API endpoints with Node.js/Inversify and MongoDB.
- Built from scratch admin platform for managing platform's database entities and users using React, Node.js, and Mongoose.
- Implemented complex UI components with React/TypeScript and SCSS.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Engineering

2006 - 2010

Tokyo Institute of Technology

Bachelor of Computer Science

2012 - 2015

University of Tokyo